Animation = {};
Animation.trivia = true;
Animation.giftDrop = 400;
Animation.mobile = {}
Animation.mobile.width = '1200px';
Animation.mobile.message = '250px';
Animation.mobile.gift = 200;
Animation.video = { height: "128.5", width: "211.2", display: false };
Animation.special_gift = ['bear', 'star-new', 'box'];
Animation.question_set = [
  {
    "question":"Who told Joseph the baby's name was to be Jesus?",
    "answers":["Mary", "His Father", "It was his decision", "An Angel"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"How many wise men came to see Jesus?",
    "answers":["3 or More", "One", "Two", "Only 3"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of these is NOT a name for Jesus in the bible",
    "answers":["Emmanuel", "the Mighty God", "the Price of Peace", "Isaac"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"What is Myrrh?",
    "answers":["A drink", "A Food", "Spice used for burrying people", "Money"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question":"Where did the wise men find Jesus",
    "answers":["In a Manger", "In a stable", "In a Temple", "In a house"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"What is a heavenly host ",
    "answers":["An Angel Army", "An Angel Choir", "The angel at the gate of heaven", "None of the above"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"When the Angel came to Mary about Jesus, Mary and Joseph were..?",
    "answers":["Married", "Engaged", "Not related at all", "Cousins"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"Christmas has always been observed",
    "answers":["July 4th", "In peak of winter", "December 25", "It changes every year"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question":"What song did the Angel's sing?",
    "answers":["Joy to the world", "O little town of Bethlehem", "They did not sing they said", "Amazin Grace"],
    "correct": 2
  },

  {
    "question":"What are Magi",
    "answers":["Astrologers", "Magicians", "Fortune tells", "Kings from Greece"],
    "correct": 0
  }
]
